Whereas the ANY key will return a set of
records matching a WHERE clause in a subquery,
you may want to know if you have a
subset of data to where every record
matches the same or similar criteria. We
can do this using the ALL keyword. I will
take the query I used with the ANY keyword and
change ANY to ALL. We will only see results if
every product has had an order with a quantity
of at least ten. I will execute this query,
and we have no records. I will change
the number in the criteria from ten
to one. Upon executing this again, still no
records. However, if I change the ALL back to ANY,
we see that 266 of our products have sold at
least one time. This next part has nothing to
do with the ANY or ALL keywords. However, we may
want to compare how many products were sold versus
how many we have in a real-life situation. I will
select just the portion of the query that deals
with the Production.Product table and execute it.
We have 504 products. Two hundred sixty-six have
sold. One may want to see what is going on
with the rest of the products in real life.